Finding Aid for the Mae Babitz papers LSC.1740
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 6. Artwork, ca. 1930-1980
  - Condemned Building, 1951 (Box 23)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil, and watercolor on watercolor paper, 22" × 30"
  - Bunker Hill Views, Grand and First, site demolished, 1951-1953 (Box 23)
  - Amestoy Building, Horizontal, Main Street near Commercial, site demolished, 1958 (Box 23)
    Crow quill and ink, and pencil on watercolor paper, 20 1/4" × 30 1/4"
  - Watts Tower, Cultural Heritage, ca. 1950s (Box 23)
    Serigraph hand painted with oil pastels on watercolor paper, 22 1/2" × 30 3/4"
  - Bunker Hill, 2nd and Grand, site demolished, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Workman Street House, Northeast Los Angeles, site demolished, 1964 (Box 23)
    Crow quill and ink, watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 30" × 22"
  - Pico House Plaza, Main Street (for Sol Babitz), Cultural Heritage, 1952-1953 (Box 23)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 18" × 24"
  - San Francisco, Divisadero and Oaks, 1951 (Box 23)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 22" × 26"
  - The Demolition of Los Angeles, sites demolished (with original wallpaper from sites), 1959-1972 (Box 24)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil, and gouache on press board, 33" × 44"
  - Bradbury Building Memories, 3rd and Broadway, Cultural Heritage, 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - Verona, Piazza Dante, 1970-1973 (Box 24)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil, watercolor, and oil paint on watercolor paper, 27 1/2" × 38 1/2"
  - Los Angeles Main Street, Main Street Phantasy, Cuida, 1954-1955 (Box 24)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and gouache on watercolor paper, 27" × 40"
  - Bradbury Building Memories, 3rd and Broadway, Cultural Heritage, 1967-1968 (Box 24)
    Silkscreen with reverse imagery on watercolor paper laid down, 30 3/4" × 22 1/2"
  - Los Angeles High School, Fragment, demolition scene in progress, site demolished, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 18 1/4" × 15 1/4"
  - Los Angeles City Streets, 3rd and Broadway, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Crow quill and ink, pen, and watercolor on watercolor paper, 17 1/4" × 14 5/8"
  - County Medical Building, Northwest Corner of the Main Street Side of the Present City Hall Grounds, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Crow quill and ink, and pen on watercolor paper, 17 1/4" × 13 1/4"
  - Los Angeles Lamppost and Pacific Electric Car (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Figueroa Neighborhood House, small, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Fire House, view from Plaza Street and L.A. Corner, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Crow quill and ink, and pencil on watercolor paper, 25" × 17 1/2"
  - Man with mustache (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Pencil on paper, 17 3/4" × 11 3/4"
  - Perez Prado (recto), sketch San Francisco house (verso) (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Pencil and ink on paper, 18" × 11 7/8"
  - Portrait of a woman (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 17 3/4" × 12"
  - Stravinsky in yellow, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Pencil and marker on watercolor paper, 19" × 11"
  - Stravinsky in black (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 20" × 13"
  - Stravinsky in pencil, profile, November 18, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 11 1/4" × 15 1/4"
  - Right side profile of man, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mask, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 13" × 16"
  - Profile of man (recto), three-quarter profile of man (verso) (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Pencil on paper, 12" × 18"
  - Man with mustache on one leg (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Pencil on paper, 17 3/4" × 11 3/4" (lower right hand corner cut out)
  - Evie (recto), nude woman (verso), undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 19 3/4" × 13"
  - Music #3, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 14 1/2" × 20"
  - Beach scene with three women, a baby and a bird (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on paper, 14" × 17"
  - Vienna, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 12" × 16 1/2"
  - Plaza, 1945-1948 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 15" × 18"
  - Musicians sketched on the backs of bank checks (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Pencil on bank checks taped to paper, 14 5/8" × 11 3/8"
  - Portrait: Bob Craft and sketch of two men, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 12 3/4" × 19 3/4"
  - Sol Babitz at TV, October 11, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 13" × 10" (folded)
  - Blue and red landscape (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Watercolor on craft paper, 11 3/4" × 18"
  - Cliffs and cove with sailboats (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on craft paper, 12 1/2" × 13 3/4"
  - Staircase, arches and columns, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Pencil and watercolor on paper, 11 3/4" × 15 3/4"
  - Residenz Palace (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Londres, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on crate paper, 15" × 12.5"
  - Red and Green landscape, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Watercolor on craft paper, 12 3/4" × 18"
  - Jack's Turkish Baths (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Crow quill and ink and watercolor on watercolor paper, 15 1/4" × 11"
  - Light House Mission, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 12" × 18"
  - Ischia, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 12" × 15"
  - Street scene, merchant shops in color (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 12" × 18"
  - Downtown Los Angeles street scene at Hotel Rosslyn, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Sketches of faces, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Sketch of lampposts, unfinished, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Pencil on paper, 15" × 11" (folded)
  - Street scene with woman and man at Engine 23 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on paper, 12" × 18"
  - Woman in coat, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on paper, 12" × 11 1/2"
  - Sketch of cathedral, unfinished, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Pencil on paper, 14 1/2" × 10 3/4"
  - Los Angeles, houses (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Rooftops, antennas and phone wires, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 11 1/4" × 15 3/4"
  - Hollywood collage, sketches, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Multiple sketches of houses and trees (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 12 1/2" × 17" (upper right corner cut out)
  - Victorian houses in red, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 18" × 12"
  - Main Street, Good Fellow's Grotto, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 11" × 15"
  - Face, sketch (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Pen and ink on paper, 15" × 10"
  - San Francisco houses (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Pencil on paper, 18" × 12"
  - Rural landscape with highway (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Watercolor and pencil, 12" × 18"
  - Vase and flowers (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 18 1/2" × 12"
  - Seaside buildings with arches (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 12"x 18"
  - Street scene with hotels, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 12" × 18"
  - Houses, car and pasture with two people, 1942-1943 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Tucson street scene (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 13 1/2" by 10"
  - Corner of abandoned building interior, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 18" × 12"
  - Green and brown figure standing in front of white arch and vases, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Watercolor on paper, 15" × 12"
  - Rocking chair on outdoor porch with arches, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 16" × 12"
  - Rural landscape with trees in foreground (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 12" × 18"
  - Rural landscape with road and telephone wires (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 12" × 18'
  - Rural landscape with trees and lake (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Right hand (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Oil paint on paper, 12" × 18"
  - Flowering tree (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 20" × 12"
  - Face in pink (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Crow quill and ink and watercolor on paper, 15" × 19 3/4"
  - Street scene with lampposts and telephone poles, Fog Horse Liquors at left, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 15" × 19 3/4"
  - Beach scene with five people (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Watercolor on paper, 12" × 18"
  - Dancing people in blue and green (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Water color and pencil on paper, 15" × 18" (torn on left side)
  - Woman dancing with green background, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 14 1/2" × 15 3/4"
  - European street with buildings and trees, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Oil paint on board, 12" × 16 1/4"
  - Three standing figures (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Watercolor and oil paint on paper, 18" × 14"
  - Factory scene with telephone poles and cyclist (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Pencil and watercolor on paper, 15" × 18"
  - Piper's Opera street scene (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil, 5 1/2" × 20 1/2"
  - Woman in front of Wayman Hotel street scene, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 15" × 20"
  - Jazz Man Records (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 14 3/4" × 20"
  - Figure drawings, early works, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Pencil on paper, 15 items
  - Figure drawings, early works, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Figure drawings, early works, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Pencil on paper, 17 items
  - Prints of Pueblo (Box 25, Folder 16)
    10 items
  - Bradbury Building Memories, 3rd and Broadway, Cultural Heritage, 1967-1968 (Box 26)
    Crow quill and ink, and watercolor on watercolor paper (original illustration), 30 3/4" × 22 1/2"
  - Rome, Trinita dei Monti, 1977 (Box 26)
    Pencil, watercolor, and gouache on artist board, 28" × 39"
  - Verona, 1970-1973 (Box 26)
    Crow quill and ink, and watercolor on artist board
  - Italian Scene, Montage of Cremona, 1970-1972 (Box 27)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper (on board), 27" × 24"
  - Campidoglio plaza, undated (Box 28)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 30" × 22"
  - 10 minutes, June 7, 1960 (Box 28)
    Pencil on paper, 24" × 18"
  - House, tree and telephone pole, unfinished, undated (Box 28)
    Pencil on paper, 22" × 30"
  - Palm trees and buildings in background, 1970 (Box 28)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 18" × 24"
  - Victorian house, unfinished, undated (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 22" × 30"
  - Freiburg, 1963 (Box 28)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 30" × 22"
  - Unknown building with spires, unfinished (Box 28)
    Pencil on paper, 28 1/2" × 20"
  - Hotel des Grands Hommes, unfinished, undated (Box 28)
  - Venice, ca. 1941-1955 (Box 28)
    Ink on paper, Ink on paper, 10 1/2" × 8 1/4"
  - Carroll Street House, Cultural Heritage, 1964 (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink on watercolor paper, 30" × 22"
  - Sunset and Hill Street, site demolished, 1957 (Box 28)
  - Regensburg, April 17, 1962 (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and oil paint on watercolor paper, 22" × 27"
  - Paris Cathedral, 1963 (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink, and gouache on watercolor paper, 22" × 30"
  - Paris, 1963 (Box 28)
  - Victorian houses on a hill (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 19 1/2" × 22"
  - Andersen Victorian house with trees, 1957 (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 22 1/4" × 30 3/4"
  - Two men with piano and violin, February 22, 1960 (Box 28)
  - A View of Perez Prado, December 1953 (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 22 1/4" × 15 1/4"
  - Scene of Europe, undated (Box 28)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 20" × 30 1/2"
  - Two women in green blouses with drinks, undated (Box 28)
    Oil paint on stretched canvas on cardboard, 23 1/2" × 18 3/4"
  - Bridge scene with buildings in background, undated (Box 28)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 22" × 30"
  - Unknown Cathedral, 1962 (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink and watercolor on watercolor paper, 15 1/2" × 15 3/4"
  - Boyle Heights (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink on watercolor paper, 15" × 20"
  - Los Angeles Lugo House, 1950 (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 14 3/4" × 20"
  - Dr. Blass', 1944 (Box 28)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 14 7/16" × 19 3/4"
  - Four-legged green and purple man, 1942 (Box 28)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 22" × 15"
  - Castelar and Ord (Box 28)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on cardboard, 16 1/4" × 20"
  - Postscape 2, undated (Box 28)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 30" × 22"
  - Man sitting, sketch, June 14, 1960 (Box 28)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 21 3/4" × 27"
  - Building interior, partly demolished, undated (Box 28)
  - Back of woman sitting, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 12" × 9"
  - Original LA High School 1873-1949 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 13" × 8"
  - Victorian house in five colors, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 12 1/4" × 10 1/4"
  - Bridge and buildings, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Oil paint on watercolor paper, 9 1/2" × 11 3/4"
  - Gothic archways (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Crow quill and ink, oil paint and pencil on watercolor paper, 9 1/2" × 7 1/4"
  - Amsterdam, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 10 1/2" × 14 3/4"
  - Men on park benches, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Pen, pencil and watercolor on paper, 10 1/2" × 10"
  - Orange columns and arches (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Crow quill and ink and watercolor on watercolor paper, 12 1/2" × 10"
  - Girl with Crucifix, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Pencil on paper, 14" × 11"
  - City Lights Number 5, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 9" × 10 3/4"
  - Cubist house in blue (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 12" × 10 1/4"
  - Portrait, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 11 3/4" × 9"
  - Man playing classical bass, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on paper, 7" × 5"
  - Catalog Melrose & Stratis (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 10" × 7"
  - Cello, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Watercolor on paper, 12" × 9"
  - Man with scarf and book, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 11" × 6 1/2"
  - City Lights table of contents (unfinished), 1953 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Pencil on paper, 9" × 10 3/4"
  - Marigold (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Watercolor on paper, 11 1/2" × 4 3/4"
  - Man in red with scarf and book (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Woman dancing, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 9" × 6 1/2"
  - Palm trees and pink sky (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 10 1/2" × 14 3/4"
  - Desert Shrubs, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 9" × 12"
  - Purple and brown landscape, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Collage, teacup, fly, vegetables, triangles, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 9" × 12"
  - Berlin Synagogue (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Crow quill and ink on watercolor paper, 9" × 10 1/2"
  - Violet and Goldie Mae, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 10 1/8" × 12 1/2"
  - Over the Seine, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper matted to envelope, 10" × 13"
  - Palm tree and street corner with cars and telephone poles (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Watercolor and pencil on paper, 14" × 11"
  - Woman and vegetable stand (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 12" × 9"
  - Nicole R., profile of woman (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Pencil on card stock, 6" × 9"
  - Grubbing (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 13 1/8" × 7 7/8"
  - Two people talking in Hamburg (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Ink on paper,
  - Miguel (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 10 1/2" × 10"
  - Sol Babitz in Ojai, profile, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 11 7/8" × 8 15/16"
  - Three women in hats, January 4, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Woman in a red jacket at a hotel (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 12 3/4" × 6"
  - Two men at a bar, Neinhaus, Gottingen, January 6, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Reeperbahn, Hamburg, January 4, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 10 1/2" × 8 1/4"
  - Woman playing recorder, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Pencil on paper, 8 1/4" × 6"
  - Albani Bier, Gottingen (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Mme Ehlers (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Pencil on paper, 8 7/8" × 11 7/8"
  - Two faces, unfinished, Hamburg (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - John Crown playing piano (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 10" × 10 1/2"
  - Man playing violin in color (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Watercolor on card stock, 9 1/2" × 6 1/2"
  - Conductor and orchestra, sketch (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 10" × 13"
  - Man at slot machine (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Pencil on paper, 12 1/4" × 9 1/2" (folded)
  - Man reclined, reading (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Pencil on paper, 8 1/2" × 11"
  - Nadia Boulanger (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Pencil on card stock, 9" × 7"
  - Man playing violin, sketch (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Pencil on paper, 11" × 8 1/2"
  - 18th Century Music (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Portrait of man with mustache, sketch (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Pencil on paper, 12" × 9"
  - Lili Kraus (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Pencil on paper (folded flier) 6" × 9"
  - Dem Devil Grass Blues (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Pencil on card stock, 11" × 8 1/2"
  - Profile outline of a man, unfinished (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Pencil on paper, 11 7/8" × 8 7/8"
  - Profile of woman at table (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Chico Rivera (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Pencil and watercolor on paper, 12 1/2" × 7"
  - Wingy Manone jazz scene (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Crow quill and pencil on paper, 9 1/4" × 8 1/4"
  - Monteverdi Bob Craft, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Six faces, sketch, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Figure drawings, early works (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Pencil on paper, 18 items
  - Prints of County Medical Building (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Prints of Sunset and Hill Street Los Angeles, 1957 (Box 30)
    4 Items
  - Unknown European buildings, outline, unfinished, undated (Box 30)
    Pencil on paper, 30" × 22"
  - Chiesa san Petronio, Bologna, 1978 (Box 30)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 19" × 26"
  - Edam, Van Gogh, October 8, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Two religious figures, gothic style, undated (Box 30)
    Watercolor and oil paint on watercolor paper, 18" × 24"
  - Chapel Tubingen (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 26" × 19 1/2"
  - Sorrento, 1974 (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 20" × 24 3/4"
  - Prints of Los Angeles northeast corner of 4th and Main, 1964 (Box 30)
    8 Items
  - Italian scene, unknown cathedral, 1970-1973 (Box 30)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 22 1/2" × 26"
  - Bonn, 1963 (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 22 1/4" × 30 1/4"
  - Cathedral spires, October 6, 1961 (Box 30)
    Pencil on paper, 19 1/2" × 20 1/2"
  - European buildings, undated (Box 30)
  - Deo Gloria, unfinished, undated (Box 30)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 19" × 26"
  - Mittenwald, 1962 (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 16 1/2" × 22 1/2"
  - Gold brushstrokes and splatter, undated (Box 30)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 19 1/2" × 25 1/2"
  - Luneberg, October 13, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Arches in a dome building, interior, unfinished, undated (Box 30)
    Pencil on paper, 25 1/2" × 19 1/2"
  - Colosseum, 1963 (Box 30)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 19 1/2" × 20 1/2"
  - Road, telephone poles and trees, undated (Box 30)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 15 1/4" × 22"
  - European street scene outline, undated (Box 30)
  - Wussenbuttel, 1961 (Box 30)
  - St. Stephan's Wien (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 27" × 21 /12"
  - Cathedral roof top, unfinished, undated (Box 30)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 19 1/2" × 25 1/2"
  - Burgtor, Lubeck, undated (Box 30)
    Pencil on paper, 26 1/2" × 19 1/2"
  - Stone arch, undated (Box 30)
    Crow quill and ink, watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 24" × 18"
  - Cathedral in orange, red and green (Box 30)
    Watercolor and oil paint on watercolor paper, 30 1/2" × 22 1/4"
  - View From Besagon Champre, undated (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 22" × 27"
  - European buildings, outline, unfinished, 1963 (Box 30)
    Pencil on paper, 19 1/2" × 25 1/4"
  - Cathedral, undated (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 19 1/2" × 26"
  - United States Capitol, undated (Box 30)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 22 1/4" × 30 1/2"
  - European buildings in color, undated (Box 30)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 21 3/4" × 27"
  - People in orange and yellow (recto) people in orange and yellow (verso), undated (Box 30)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 27" × 16 1/2" (folded)
  - Los Angeles Scene 12, 1945-1946 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink and watercolor, 15 1/4" × 22 1/4"
  - Victorian corner house in white pink and blue, 1957 (Box 31)
    Pencil and chalk on paper, 18 1/4" × 2 1/4"
  - Victorian house in yellow, green and brown, 1957 (Box 31)
    Pencil and chalk on paper, 19" × 24 3/4"
  - Trees, lamppost, arches and purple stairs, 1957 (Box 31)
    Pencil and chalk, 18" × 24"
  - Rural scene with houses, road, trees and mountains, February 1956 (Box 31)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 22" × 18 1/4"
  - Undefined building, undated (Box 31)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 22 1/2" × 15"
  - Sunday Morning, Central at 12th St., 1942 (Box 31)
    Pencil on paper, 17 3/4" × 23 7/8"
  - Hollywood Freeway Scene, 1953 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 15" × 20"
  - LA Street Scene, Sunset near Silverlake, undated (Box 31)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 15" × 20"
  - Palm trees in green, blue and purple (Box 31)
    Watercolor on watercolor paper, 18" × 24"
  - Rectangular wood home, woman in window, and sidewalk, 1942 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 12" × 22"
  - Trees in yellow and green, undated (Box 31)
    Pencil and chalk, 20" × 26"
  - Los Angeles #12, 1945-1955 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 15" × 22 1/2"
  - Il Duomo Parma (Box 31)
  - Piazza Erbe Mantova, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Piazza Geribaldi Parma, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Unknown cathedral, interior, 1970 (Box 31)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 18" × 21 1/2"
  - Bar Giuseppe, 1974 (Box 31)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 15" × 22"
  - Arched doorway, undated (Box 31)
    Pencil on watercolor paper, 21 1/4" × 13 1/2"
  - Statue of man on horse and building with arches in background, undated (Box 31)
    Pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 18" × 24"
  - Hillside buildings, bill board and palm trees, 1957 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 22" × 29 3/4"
  - Lamppost with buildings, 1950-1957 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on watercolor paper, 22" × 10 3/4"
  - Victorian house scene with woman in pink and man in blue, undated (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on watercolor paper, 20" × 26"
  - Street scene with lampposts in brown, green and red, 1955 (Box 31)